In this exercise, we're going to explore Bower in a lot of detail.
在这个练习里面 我们会探索 Bower 的大量细节
Now, we're going to, first, install Bower on our computer.
首先我们要在电脑里安装 Bower
Then, we will use Bower to go and fetch bootstrap and
然后 我们我们会使用 Bower 来自动获取 Bootstrap
find awesome for us automatically.
以及 Font Awesome
Then, finally, we are going to make use of the components that
最后 我们要把这些通过 Bower 获取的组件
Bower has already fetched, in our web page.
用在我们的网页上
Now, you're gonna ask, we already have the Fantasm files,
现在你可能会问 我们已经有Font Awesome的文件
we already have the Bootstrap files, why do you need to do it all over again?
我们也已经有Bootstrap的文件了 为什么又要重新再来一次呢 ?
The primary reason for
主要的原因是
doing is exercise, is to learn how Bower automates this process.
了解 Bower 如何将这个过程自动化的
Of course, as we go through the next few courses it becomes increasingly
当然 在接下来的几课中
clear to you why these tools are very,
你会越来越清楚地看到
very essential to get your workflow organized.
为什么这些工具对你工作流程的系统化是至关重要的
When we install Bower, we need to install Bower as a global
安装 Bower 的时候 我们需要将它安装为
node competent or global node module.
全局 Node 组件 或者说全局 Node 模块
So to do that we have to type on the command line, we'll say
要做到这点 我们要在命令行中输入
npm install -g for global.
npm install -g -g的意思是全局(global)
And then, we'll say bower.
然后 再输入 bower
Now, again, remember, if you are doing this on a Mac or
再一次提醒 如果你在用 Mac 或者 Linux 机器的话
a Linux machine, then you should precede this with the sudo command.
那你要在这个命令前面加上 sudo 命令
So since I am working on a Mac,
因为我在用 Mac
I'm gonna add the sudo to this.
所以我把 sudo 命令加在这里
And then, when you hit the return [BLANK
然后按下回车键
AUDIO] and sit back and
稍等一下
wait until note goes in Fetches Bower and installs it as a global module.
直到 Node 把 Bower 下载完成并且安装为全局模块
Once the installation is completed then Bower is ready for you to use.
安装完成后 Bower 就可以使用了
We saw that MPM was making use of this manifest file called package.json.
我们看到 NPM 利用了这个叫做 package.json 的清单文件
Similarly, Bower uses a file called bower.json which
与此相似 Bower 也利用一个叫做 bower.json 的文件
keeps track of all the components that you are making use in your current project.
来追踪你在当前项目中使用的所有组件
So we will build the bower.json file.
我们会建立这个 bower.json 文件
So to do that, you could simply look at an existing bower.json file and
要做到这一点 你可以打开一个已有的 bower.json 文件
then copy it in.
然后复制里面的内容
Now, the way I would show you to build a bower.json file,
现在我要向你展示的建立 bower.json 文件的方法
is to use the Bower Init command.
是使用 bower init 命令
So when you type bower init on the command prompt, it'll ask you
当你在命令提示符窗口里输入 bower init 的时候
a bunch of questions and then initialize the bower.adjacent file for you.
它会问你一系列的问题 并且为你初始化 bower.json 文件
So let's go through that process next.
让我们过一下这个流程
For the name I'm just gonna use the name confusion.
名字的话我会用 conFusion
That's the web project that we have been building so far.
这是我们到目前为止一直在构建的网站项目
And version number, I'll say 1.
至于版本号 我会用1
For the author name,
到作者名
you can type in your own name, it doesn't matter, whatever you want to type.
你可以输入你自己的名字 这不重要 输入什么都可以
Once you have typed in all the answers to the questions that Bower asks,
当你输入完 Bower 所有提问的答案时
we will have a bower.json file created for you.
就有一个 bower.json 文件为你建立好了
Now this bower.json file is in the confusion folder.
现在这个 bower.json 文件在 conFusion 文件夹里
Let's now examine the contents of the bower.json file.
让我们检查一下这个 bower.json 文件的内容
That we just created.
就是刚刚建立的这个
So inside this file I have opened it in brackets here.
在这个我刚刚用 Brackets 打开的文件里
So we can see that it contains all the information that we typed in.
可以看到它包含了我们输入的所有信息
This file is stored in the JSON format.
这个文件以 JSON 的格式存储
So it's always a keyword and the value there.
所以它总是一个关键词和一个值的配对
Inside this file you can notice that the name has been given as confusion, version,
在这个文件里你会留意到 "name" 已经被赋值为 "conFusion"
description, what we just typed in when we typed power in it and
还有 "vesion" "description" 都是我们输入 bower init 之后
answered the questions.
回答的问题
So we have all this information captured here.
因此这里保存了所有的这些信息
And now, we are going to install some
现在 我们准备要安装一些
components that we need in order to build this webpage.
构建网站所需的组件
Let's now see how we can make use of Bower to install bootstrap.
让我们来看看怎么利用 Bower 来安装 Bootstrap
To do that, at the command line type,
要做到这个 我们要在命令行中输入
bower install bootstrap with a -S.
bower install bootstrap -S
Now, the -S is used to save this information into my bower.json file.
这个 -S 的参数是把安装信息保留到我的 bower.json 文件的
Now, after I finish these,
当我完成了安装
we are gonna examine the bower.json file to understand how it has been updated.
我们可以检查一下 bower.json 文件 看看它是怎样被更新的
So let's hit the return and watch Bower go and fetch bootstrap files for us.
让我们按下回车键 观察 Bower 为我们获取 Bootstrap 的文件
Now, when Bower fetches the bootstrap files from the git depository,
当 Bower 从 git 仓库 (git depository) 中获取 Bootstrap 文件时
it realizes that Bower depends on jquery.
它发现 Bower 依赖于 jQuery
So Bower will automatically go and fetch jquery and then solve it for us.
因此 Bower 会自动获取 jQuery 为我们解决这个依赖问题
The next thing that we need is font-awesome.
下一个我们需要的是 font-awesome
So to fetch font-awesome, we'll type bower
要获取 font-awesome, 我们要在命令提示符窗口里输入
install font-awesome -S, at the prompt.
bower install font-awesome -S
[BLANK AUDIO] Sit back and wait for
坐下来慢慢等
Bower to go and fetch the font-awesome files.
等 Bower 为我们获取 font-awesome 文件
There you go.
好了。
We have everything that we need to go ahead with our project now.
我们准备好了所有东西 可以继续我们的项目了
In order to understand what Bower did, let's go to our confusion folder and
为了理解 Bower 做了什么 让我们进入 conFusion 文件夹
then you will notice that in the conFusion folder
你会留意到 conFusion 文件夹里
there is a folder there named bower_components, so
有一个文件夹叫做 bower_components
let's go into the bower_components folder and see what it contains.
让我们进入 bower_components 文件夹 看看里面有什么
Going into the bower_components folder,
进入 bower_components 文件夹之后
you'll notice that is has three folders there.
你会看到这里有三个文件夹
Bootstrap, font-awesome and jquery.
分别是 bootstrap, font-awesome 以及 jquery
Let's navigate into bootstrap to see what is there inside the folder.
让我们进入到 bootstrap 文件夹 看看里面有什么
Inside the bootstrap folder, you can see that it contains a whole lot of files.
在 bootstrap 文件夹里 你可以看到里面有一大堆文件
You can also notice that there is a package.json file there.
你会留意到这里有一个 package.json 文件
Something that we are familiar with there is power of adjacent file there.
这是我们所熟悉的 然后还有一个 bower.json 文件
In particular what is of interest to me is this folder called dist.
尤其让我感兴趣的这个叫做 dist 的文件
That is the distribution folder that contains bootstrap files,
这是一个包含了 bootstrap 文件的发布 (distribution) 文件夹
that can be directly used in our webpage.
可以直接用在我们的网页上
So navigating to the distribution folder, you see the three folders there,
当我们进入这个 distribution 文件夹 你会看到里面有三个文件夹
css, fonts, and js.
分别是 css, fonts 和 js
Remember when we first fetched bootstrap as a ZIP file,
记得我们最初下载 ZIP 文件形式的 Bootstrap 时
this is what was contained in that Bootstrap ZIP file.
这个 Bootstrap 的 ZIP 文件就包含了这些东西
So going into the css folder, you can see all the bootstrap files there.
因此当我们进入 css 文件夹 你会看到所有的 Bootstrap 文件
Similarly, the JavaScript and the fonts folders.
js文件夹和fonts文件夹也一样
Going back up we can now see, inside the font-awesome folder, you again see
回到上级目录 进入 font-awesome 文件夹 你会再一次看到
all the font-awesome files that we fetched earlier from downloading the ZIP file.
里面有早前我们下载的 font-awesome 的 ZIP 压缩包里面的所有内容
They're already here for us.
它们已经在这里了
Bower did all the work behind the scenes for us and fetched all the files.
Bower 在幕后为我们完成了所有工作 获取了所有文件
Similarly, as I mentioned to you,
相似地 就像我提到的那样
bower realizes that bootstrap is dependent on jQuery.
Bower 发现 Bootstrap 依赖于 jQuery
So bower will automatically go and fetch jQuery for us, and
于是它就自动地为我们获取了 jQuery
install it into the bower competence folder.
将它安装在 bower_components 文件夹里
So now you see the jquery folder there.
所以你可以看到 jquery 文件夹在这里
And inside the jquery folder, you have the distribution folder,
而 jquery 文件夹里面 有一个 distribution 文件夹
which contains the jquery JavaScript files there.
里面包含了 jQuery 的 JavaScript 文件
Now, getting back to the conFusion folder, we are now going to go and
现在 回到 conFusion 文件夹 我们准备要
examine the contents of the bower.json file that we had seen earlier.
检查一下我们之前看到的 bower.json 文件的内容了
Getting back to the bower.json file, if you scroll down, you'll notice that
回到这个 bower.json 文件 如果你向下滚动 你会发现
bower has installed some additional information into the bower.json file.
Bower 写入了一些额外的信息到这个 bower.json 文件
Here, this information is stored under the keyboard dependencies.
在这里 这些信息存储在 "dependencies" (依赖) 关键词下
Inside there it has noted that bootstrap
这个关键词下面记录了 bootstrap
3.3.5, that is version 3.3.5,
3.3.5 也就是3.3.5版
and font-awesome version 4.4.0.
而 font-awesome则是版本4.4.0
Now, bower has already noted in the bower adjacent file that this
现在 Bower已经在 bower.json 文件中
particular project depends upon Bootstrap and Font-Awesome.
记录下这个特定的项目依赖于 Bootstrap 和 Font-Awesome
And so that's what is noted in the dependencies there.
这就是记录在 "dependencies" (依赖) 那里的信息
You're gonna ask me, what is the use of this bower.json file?
你会问 bower.json 文件有什么用?
Let me show that to you in a minute.
我很快就会把它的用处展示给你看
Let's now go back to our conFusion folder and then go inside the bower_components.
让我们先回到 conFusion 文件夹 然后进入 bower_components 文件夹
I'm going to select all these folders and then delete them.
我将选中所有这些文件夹然后把它们删除
And then, we will make bower go and fetch all these for us.
然后我们让 Bower 帮我们把所有这些东西下载回来
[BLANK AUDIO] Now, we have cleaned out the bower_components folder.
现在 我们已经清空了 bower_components 文件夹
Now, if we want bower to install all this, we can go at the command line.
如果想要 Bower 来安装所有这些东西 我们可以去命令行
We just type bower install, and the bower will automatically go and
只需要输入 bower install, Bower就会自动
fetch all the packages for you, and install them in the bower_complex folder.
为你获取所有的程序包 并且把它们安装在 bower_components 文件夹里面
So now if I type bower install [BLANK AUDIO] and
现在我输入 bower install
hit the Return, bower will take care of installing all the files for us.
按下回车键, Bower 就会为我们照料好安装所有文件的过程
How does bower know where to find the information
Bower 是怎么知道去哪里找
about the packages that it needs to install?
要安装的程序包的信息的呢?
That is where the bower.json file comes to our rescue.
这就是 bower.json 的威力所在
Recall that in the bower.json file, we have the dependencies already noted there.
记得在 bower.json 文件里面 已经记录下了依赖关系
So when you say bower install, bower is going to consult the bower.json file, and
所以当你输入 bower install 的时候 Bower 就会去查询这个 bower.json 文件
then sees that this particular project is dependent on Bootstrap and Font-Awesome.
它就会看到当前项目依赖于 Bootstrap 和 Font-Awesome
So it's gonna go and fetch all those components for us.
然后它就会为我们获取些组件
Now, when we go back to our bower_components folder,
现在 我们回到 bower_components 文件夹
you again see all those files reappear.
你会发现所有文件都重新出现了
Now, you must be wondering, what's the use of all this?
现在 你应该会想知道 这些文件都有什么用呢?
If you are working on large projects,
在开发大项目时
very often you will have a team of people working on this project.
经常是一组人一起开发
And these files have to be version controlled, so
这些文件必须有版本控制
you might use a git repository,
你可能会用 git 仓库 (git repository)
or a some form of version control system where you'll be checking in these files.
或者某种形式的版本控制系统来登记这些文件
Now, when you check in the files, all these bootstrap, font-awesome,
当你登记这些文件 诸如 Bootstrap, Font-Awesome
and jquery files do not need to be stored in your version control system,
还有 jQuery 之类的文件就不必存储在你的版本控制系统里面
because they are not dependent, you are not changing them in any way.
因为它们没有依赖 你也没有改变它们
So the only things that you install in your version control system
唯一需要安装在你的版本控制系统里面的东西
are the HTML and JavaScript and CSS files that you created.
就是你创建的 HTML, JavaScript 和 CSS 文件
In addition, you're gonna install your bower.json file also.
除此之外 你还要设置好你的 bower.json 文件
In your version control system.
在你的版本控制系统里
So somebody else, who wants to recreate that
这样 如果别人想在他的电脑里重现
project folder structure on their own computer, can simply go to the VCS,
这个工程文件夹的结构 他们只需要去VCS
the version control system, and then fetch all the files to their machine.
也就是版本控制系统 把所有文件下载到他们的机器里
And then, once they get that, since they already have the bower.json file,
完成这一步之后 既然他们已经获得了 bower.json 文件
they can simply type bower install at the command prompt, and
他们就可以直接在命令提示符窗口里输入 bower install
then bower will take care of fetching all the files for you.
Bower 就会照料好获取依赖文件的过程
The same thing applies even for node packages that you use.
同样的事情对 Node 的程序包也适用
If you are using node packages that are stored locally,
当你使用了存储在本地的 Node 程序包
remember that we had created a packaged or adjacent file earlier.
记得我们之前创建了一个叫做 package.json 的文件
If you type nvm install, nvm will consult your package or
如果你输入 npm install, npm 会查询你的 package.json 文件
adjacent file and go and fetch all the node components that you need.
然后为你获取所需的 Node 组件
And then, or node modules that you need, and then install them.
或者是 Node 模块 然后将它们全部安装好
That's where the power comes to our rescue.
这就是 Bower 的威力 （power） 所在
Sorry, that was not a pun intended.
抱歉 这并不是一个故意的双关语
Now, when we go back to examine our folder,
现在 当我们回去查看我们的文件夹
using either brackets of any text editor,
用 Brackets 或者任何其他文本编辑器
you would notice that the bower_components folder has appeared there.
你会发现 bower_components 文件夹已经出现了
So we can simply go in there and then in the distribution folder,
进入这个文件夹 然后在发布 (distribution) 文件夹里
we already see the css, fonts and js fonts there.
我们已经可以看到 css, fonts 和 js 文件夹了
So in our index.html page where we were using the CSS and
在我们的 index.html 文件中 我们曾经使用早前下载的
the JavaScript files that we fetched earlier,
CSS 和 JavaScript 文件
we can simply replace those referring to the files
现在我们可以简单地将这些文件替换为
in the distribution folder of the bower_components folder.
bower_components 中发布文件夹里的相应文件
So I'm going to replace each one of them by the files in
我将把这些文件的每一个替换为
the distribution folders there.
发布文件中的那些文件
Now, what's the advantage of this?
这样做有什么好处呢 ?
Again, as I've said, if you check and
再一次 就像我说过的那样 如果你把这些文件登记在版本控制系统里
somebody else downloads them, they can simply do bower install.
别人就可以下载这些文件 然后做一个 bower install 就好了
They don't need to go and manually fetch any of those bootstrap or
他们不需要手工地获取任何 Bootstrap 或者
font-awesome files.
Font-Awesome 文件
Instead, all this will be taken care of by bower for you.
相反 这个过程 Bower 已经帮你处理好了
Now, of course, this is not exactly the way we use bower,
当然这不是我们使用 Bower 的确切方式
but bower helps us to fetch all these files.
但是 Bower 可以帮我们获取所有这些文件
Later on you will see the other tools coming in.
稍后我们还会介绍其他的工具
They will help to build your webpage and then create a distribution of your own
他们会帮助你建立你的网页并且创建你自己的项目的发布包
project, at which you can then install on your web server.
然后你可以将这个发布包安装在你的网站服务器上
Hold off on that until we come to the next course.
不过下节课我们再继续讨论这个话题
But now, let's go in and make use of the files that bower has fetched for us.
现在 让我们利用 Bower 为我们获取的文件
Returning to these links,
回到这些链接
I'm gonna replace them with the files that Bower has fetched for me.
我会将它们替换为 Bower 为我获取的文件
So going in there I will type in bower_components and
所以在这里我会输入 bower_components
I will say bower- components bootstrap and
bower_components/bootstrap
then dist, and then enter Return.
然后 dist 然后回车
That's it.
仅此而已 【教育无边界字幕组】翻译：拖延菌 | 校对：鸭肉松 | 审阅：|就这样
So instead of using the css files in the project css folder I am instead using
这样 替代使用项目文件夹中 css 文件夹里面的 css 文件
Competence files that have been fetched for me.
这里使用了 Bower 自动获取的 bower_components 里面的文件
Same thing I'm gonna do with the bootstrap theme and
然后我会对 bootstrap-theme 文件
the font-awesome, css files, too.
font-awesome 的 CSS文件做同样的替换
So with these changes, I have now made our index.html
通过这些变动 我让 index.html 使用了
page use the ccss files that Bower has fetched for
Bower 为我们获取 并存储在 bower_components 中的
me and stored in the bower_components.
中的CSS文件
Going to the bottom of the page I'm going to replace all the JavaScript
去到页面的底部 我还要替换所有的 JavaScript 文件
files also to make use of the files that bower has fetched for me.
改为使用 Bower 获取的那些文件
So going in here, I'm going to replace this
让我们翻到那里
jquery part by saying bower_components.
我要把 jquery 部分替换为
And jquery and then dist, and
bower_components/jquery/dist
you notice that jquery min.js already exists there.
你会留意到 jquery.min.js 已经存在了
So that's the jquery file that I'm going to make use of.
那个这个 jquery 文件就是我要用的
Similarly, for the bootstrap.min I will say bower_components.
相似的 对于 bootstrap.min.js 文件 我会替换为
Bootstrap, distribution, js, and bootstrap.
bower_components/boostrap/dist/js/bootstrap.min.js
But these updates, now,
在这轮替换之后
our index.html page is using the files that bower has fetched for us.
我们的 index.html 所使用的文件 就全部都是 Bower 为我们获取的
Interim of the files that we downloaded earlier.
而不是我们早前自行下载的文件
We should do the same updates to the AboutUs.html page and
我们还要对 AboutUs.html 和
also to the ContactUs.html page.
ContactUs.html 做同样的更新
After making these changes, if we go back and
在完成这些变动之后 如果我们回去
look at our webpage, you won't find any difference.
查看我们的网页 你不会发现任何的区别
The only difference now is that your web project is using the files that Bower
唯一的区别就是 现在你的网站项目使用了 Bower 获取的文件
fetched, of the files that we downloaded earlier.
而不是我们早前下载的文件
So by making use of Bower, you can save yourself a lot of time,
因此通过使用 Bower 你可以节省很多时间
and let Bower do the work for you.
让 Bower 为你代劳
So again, having a look at the webpage, it's still exactly the same as before.
再一次 我们看一下网页 它仍然跟之前一模一样
Nothing changed, except that we are using files that power fetch.
除了我们现在使用的是 Bower 获取的文件之外 没有任何变化
So this completes this exercise where we learned how to
那么这个练习就完成了 我们学习到了
make use of power to fetch the packages and
如何使用 Bower 来自动获取
the assets that we need for our web project automatically.
我们的网站项目所需的程序包和资源文件
We're gonna explore the remaining tools in the next course.
在下一节课里 我们会探索其他的工具 翻译: LIYB  | 审阅: Saul Qunming Yuan Coursera Global Translator Community